(Amy:)See? Maybe you'll love living alone.
(Sheldon:)I don't know. Perhaps.
(Amy:)And if it turns out you don't...
you and I could live together.
(Bernadette:)You and--
Oh, sure.
(Sheldon:)And while we're at it,
why don't we get engaged, too?
(Sheldon:)Why don't we get a little house,
start a family?
(Sheldon:)Enjoy our sunset years together?
Do you hear yourself, woman?
(Amy:)-Sheldon, it was just a thought.
-No. Here's a thought.
(Sheldon:)You're not moving in,
Leonard's not moving out,
(Sheldon:)everything stays
exactly the way it is.
(Sheldon:)And by the way, I saw you make
this Strawberry Quik with syrup,
and you're supposed
to use the powder!
(Amy:)-It tastes the same.
-No. The syrup tastes better,
(Sheldon:)and I don't like it.
This is so sweet!
You never cook for me.
(Leonard:)Well, you cook for me
all the time and...
(Penny:)If you don't like my cooking,
why haven't you ever said anything?
(Leonard:)It's hard to talk
with so much heavy chewing to do.